Finding Aid for Ivory Photo, Ann Arbor, Michigan ca. 1927-1971
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Negatives-- 8"x10"
  - University of Michigan
    - Alumni Activities
      - Reunions
        - Literature, Science, and the Arts
          - Class of 1909 and Kiltie band
            - circa 1940 (Box 29)
              [see similar print]
            - 1949 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1910
            - June 15, 1940 (Box 29)
            - circa 1950, 2 negatives (Box 29)
          - Class of 1911
            - June 21, 1941 (Box 29)
            - circa 1943 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1914 1939 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1915
            - circa 1939 (Box 29)
            - June 15, 1940 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1916
            - circa 1943 (Box 29)
            - 1940s (Box 29)
          - Class of 1919 circa 1939 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1920 June 15, 1940 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1921 June 21, 1941 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1922 June 1947 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1923 1948 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1926 June 20, 1941 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1929 1939 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1933 1948 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1935 June 15, 1940 (Box 29)
        - Medical School
          - Class of 1886 -- T. Smith Kingston at reunion June 1946 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1890 June 15, 1940 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1891 circa June 21, 1941 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1894 1945 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1898 1948, 2 negatives (Box 29)
          - Class of 1901
            - 1948 (Box 29)
            - Undated (Box 29)
          - Class of 1903 May 28, 1943 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1904
            - 1939 (Box 29)
            - circa 1943 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1905 June 15, 1940 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1906
            - circa 1941 (Box 29)
            - 1945 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1907 June 1947 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1910 June 15, 1940 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1914
            - circa 1939 (Box 29)
            - circa 1943 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1915 1945 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1916 June 20, 1941 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1921
            - circa June 20, 1941 (Box 29)
            - 1945 (outside Pretzel Bell) (Box 29)
          - Class of 1924 1939 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1925 circa 1948 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1928 1948 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1930 June 15, 1940 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1934 circa 1939 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1935 June 15, 1940 (Box 29)
          - Class of 1936 circa June 21, 1941 (Box 29)
    - Athletics
      - Athletic Association -- 150-pound squad (football?) 1948 (Box 30)
      - Chinese soccer team June 12, 1939 (Box 30)
      - Intramural Building display March 30, 1939 (Box 30)
    - Buildings and Views
      - Alumni Memorial Hall
        - Interior circa 1946, 3 negatives (Box 30)
        - January 27, 1947, 2 negatives (Box 30)
      - Angell Hall September 30, 1929 (Box 30)
      - Barbour Gymnasium -- interior
        - July 25, 1940, 4 negatives (Box 30)
        - July 21, 1941, 2 negatives (Box 30)
      - Business Administration, School of -- Bureau of Industrial Relations library and office with people September 18, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 30)
      - Campus Scenes
        - Xi Psi Phi Dental Fraternity's bench September 27, 1940 (Box 30)
      - Cook (Martha) dormitory circa 1930 (Box 30)
      - Couzens Hall (dormitory) May 1, 1941 (Box 30)
      - Dental Building (Kellogg Institute)
        - December 26, 1939, 2 negatives (Box 30)
        - circa 1939 (Box 30)
      - East Quad (men's dormitory)
        - Construction December 26, 1939 (Box 30)
        - Construction circa 1939 (Box 30)
        - circa 1940 (Box 30)
        - May 1, 1941 (Box 30)
      - Fletcher Hall February 10, 1940 (Box 30)
      - Fraternities and Sororities
        - Chi Psi house (South State at Monroe) March 23, 1935 (Box 30)
        - Phi Sigma Kappa -- exterior and interior September 25, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 30)
      - Fresh Air Camp for Boys -- architectural drawing of Health Cottage August 1, 1938 (Box 30)
      - Health Service circa 1940 (Box 30)
      - Hill Auditorium -- chairs circa 1949, 2 negatives (Box 30)
      - Law School
        - Legal Research Building (Library) -- interiors October 10, 1933, 4 negatives (Box 30)
        - Old Law Building circa 1933 (Box 30)
      - Library 1930s or, circa 1940s (Box 30)
      - Medical Buildings
        - East Medical circa 1930 (Box 30)
        - West Medical circa 1929 (Box 30)
      - Michigan League circa 1929 (Box 30)
      - Michigan Union
        - Exterior and pool circa 1930, 2 negatives (Box 30)
        - Undated (Box 30)
      - Rackham Building
        - Construction site June 17, 1936, 2 negatives (Box 30)
        - June 15, 1938 (Box 30)
        - circa 1940, 2 negatives (Box 30)
      - Randall Laboratory of Physics September 6, 1939, 3 negatives (Box 30)
      - Stadium -- aerial view during game 1927 (Box 30)
      - Stockwell Hall
        - December 1, 1941 (Box 30)
        - May 1, 1941 (Box 30)
      - University Hospital circa 1939 (Box 30)
      - Vaughan (Victor) Residence May 1, 1941 (Box 30)
      - Waterman Gymnasium circa 1930 (Box 30)
      - West Quad (Men's dormitory) circa 1940 (Box 30)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Interior with piano circa 1940 (Box 30)
    - Colleges, Schools, and Other Divisions
      - Architecture and Design, College of
        - Brigham, George --testing lab, West Engineering September 1946, 8 negatives (Box 30)
        - Lapez, Carlos -- paintings circa 1948, 2 negatives (Box 30)
      - Business Administration, School of
        - Group photo August 24, 1949 (Box 30)
        - Group photo 1950 (Box 30)
      - Chemistry Department -- lecture April 10, 1940 (Box 30)
      - Dental School
        - Group photo November 4, 1941 (Box 30)
        - Group photo 1949 (Box 30)
      - Education, School of
        - Summer 1938
          - McClusky (Howard Y.?) group -- educational psychology (Box 30)
          - Olson, Dr. -- group (University High School?) (Box 30)
        - Dr. Odina B. Olson's group (University High School?) August 1, 1939 (Box 30)
        - Fourth and Fifth graders (University Elementary School?) June 13, 1941 (Box 30)
        - Dr. Olson's group (University High School?) August 5, 1941 (Box 30)
      - Engineering, College of
        - Engineering Lab -- group in wind tunnel with model plane, early circa 1930s (Box 30)
        - Mechanical Engineering Lab -- equipment circa 1949 (Box 30)
      - Forestry, Department of
        - Petrovsky Forestry Lab (wood utilization lab) -- equipment September 22, 1943, 3 negatives (Box 30)
      - Health Service -- staff
        - May 22, 1942 (Box 30)
        - May 26, 1943 (Box 30)
      - Law School -- group photos
        - 1948 (Box 30)
        - January 1949 (Box 30)
      - Library Extension Service
        - Miss Edith Thomas's book exhibit at Rackham July 9, 1941, 11 negatives (Box 30)
        - Miss Edith Thomas's airplane and book display at Michigan Union April 16, 1943, 2 negatives (Box 30)
        - Women in offices September 1946, 2 negatives (Box 30)
      - Physics Department
        - Professors Crane and Halpern with cyclotron September 12, 1938, 4 negatives (Box 30)
      - Speech Department
        - Broadcasting classes December 18, 1946, 5 negatives (Box 30)
      - University Broadcasting Service: Dr. Maddy's bands and choruses
        - December 12, 1932, 3 negatives (Box 30)
        - February 13, 1933 (Box 30)
        - December 10, 1934 (Box 30)
        - 1935, 6 negatives (Box 30)
      - University Hospital
        - Surgery staff June 2, 1941 (Box 30)
      - University Museums
        - Lecture -- Dr. Elmer Barry October 2, 1941, 2 negatives (Box 30)
    - Individuals and Groups
      - Alumni
        - Joe Duffy and unidentified man circa 1935 (Box 30)
      - Faculty
        - Barthell, Dr. -- Union Pool February 16, 1945, 2 negatives (Box 30)
        - Cross, Professor Arthur Lyon (in his library) and unidentified portrait July 7, 1938, 3 negatives (Box 30)
        - Slusser, Professor -- costume party February 8, 1941, 4 negatives (Box 30)
      - Staff
        - Fresh Air Camp -- staff August 14, 1939 (Box 30)
        - Motor fleet supervisors -- training course
          - 1946 (Box 30)
          - August 1947 (Box 30)
          - 1948, 2 negatives (Box 30)
          - April 18, 1949 (Box 30)
          - June 1-2, 1949 (Box 30)
        - Waiters -- West Quad May 6, 1943 (Box 30)
      - Students
        - Owen (Robert) Coop June 12, 1941 (Box 30)
        - West Quad athletic managers May 6, 1943 (Box 30)
      - Miscellaneous
        - League College 1948 (Box 30)
        - United Steel Workers circa 1947 (Box 30)
        - Women mechanics 1943, 3 negatives (Box 30)
    - Organizations
      - Emeritus Club 1939, 2 negatives
        - June 15, 1940 (Box 30)
        - June 20, 1941 (Box 30)
        - On steps of Kellogg Institute 1948 (Box 30)
        - On steps of Kellogg Institute 1950 (Box 30)
      - Turkish Army (with wives and children) April 4, 1941 (Box 30)
      - U of M Club 1947 (Box 30)
    - Special Celebrations and Events
      - Michigan Daily 50th Anniversary Banquet November 16, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 30)
    - Student Life
      - Dances
        - Ray Carry band September 19, 1938, 4 negatives (Box 30)
      - Fraternities and Sororities
        - Alpha Chi Omega October 7, 1940 (Box 30)
        - Alpha Tau Omega -- J-Hop February 12, 1933 (Box 30)
        - Nu Sigma Nu June 12, 1941 (Box 30)
        - Pi Lambda Phi -- party November 20, 1932 (Box 30)
        - Sigma Nu -- volleyball team January 6, 1940 (Box 30)
        - Sigma Phi Epsilon June 4, 1941, 2 negatives (Box 30)
        - Sigma Rho Tau circa 1940, 2 negatives (Box 30)
      - French Club August 16, 1939 (Box 30)
      - Lantern Night June 1946 (Box 30)
      - Michigamua Braves of 1923 (Box 30)
      - Newman Club -- officers May 1946, 2 negatives (Box 30)
      - Phi Lambda Upsilon April 25, 1932 (Box 30)
      - Sigma Gamma Epsilon
        - December 11, 1932 (Box 30)
        - May 9, 1934 (Box 30)
      - Theater, Michigan League -- Gloria Bondell circa 1935, 2 negatives (Box 30)
    - World War II
      - Army: Judge Advocate General's (JAG) School
        - Sixth graduation banquet 1942, 2 negatives (Box 30)
        - Eighth class
          - Group photograph January 9, 1943 (Box 30)
          - Banquet March 5, 1943, 2 negatives (Box 30)
        - Ninth class
          - Group photograph February 20, 1943 (Box 30)
          - Banquet April 16, 1943 (Box 30)
        - Tenth class
          - Group photographs March 24, 1943, 3 negatives (Box 30)
          - Banquet May 21, 1943 (Box 30)
        - Eleventh class -- group photograph May 14, 1943 (Box 30)
      - Reserve Officers' Training Corps: Major Vollrath's officers February 27, 1943, 2 negatives (Box 30)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Mannequins in armed forces uniforms and work clothes June 21, 1946, 3 negatives (Box 30)
  - Bridgewater
    - Bridgewater Machine Tool Company -- machinery and workers circa 1951, 4 negatives (Box 30)
  - Dexter
    - Dexter Public School April 28, 1940 (Box 30)
    - Map July 3, 1939 (Box 30)
    - Schlaff Farm -- 7010 Dexter Road August 19, 1933, 4 negatives (Box 30)
  - Manchester
    - Davis (C.F.) Mobilgas Station, Standard Station, and road September 2, 1939, 3 negatives (Box 30)
    - Pleasant Lake Road with gas stations and houses; auto wreck June 6, 1938, 5 negatives (Box 30)
  - Milan
    - Acme Broach Corporation -- equipment circa 1940, 2 negatives (Box 30)
    - Car wreck and street scenes December 20, 1946, 4 negatives (Box 30)
    - Railroad depot and tracks March 10, 1948, 2 negatives (Box 30)
  - Saline
    - Gross (Walter) Company -- machinery 1946, 2 negatives (Box 30)
  - Scio?
    - Scio Machine -- machine tools 1946, 2 negatives (Box 30)
  - Whitmore Lake
    - Old U.S. 23 with houses and businesses March 28, 1933, 6 negatives (Box 30)
  - Ypsilanti
    - Cleary College
      - Basketball team February 13, 1941 (Box 30)
      - Dances and parties 1941, 2 negatives (Box 30)
      - Graduation processions and banquets
        - June 14, 1937, 3 negatives (Box 30)
        - June 15, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 30)
        - June 21, 1941, 2 negatives (Box 30)
      - Orchestra February 13, 1941 (Box 30)
      - Play -- cast May 24, 1941 (Box 30)
      - Roller rink group February 14, 1941 (Box 30)
      - Students, staff, and faculty -- interior scenes 1941, 6 negatives (Box 30)
      - Women's Bowling February 13, 1941 (Box 30)
    - Michigan State Normal College -- group activity ("social recreation") February 28, 1935, 4 negatives (Box 30)
    - Ypsilanti Stove Works -- stoves 1940-1941, 4 negatives (Box 30)
    - Unidentified stone house (?) circa 1935, 3 negatives (Box 30)
  - Washtenaw County?
    - Businesses
      - Carnation Milk Company -- cow milking demonstration -- county fair? September 1, 1941, 2 negatives (Box 30)
      - White Star Dairy (barn) circa 1935 (Box 30)
    - Recreation
      - Roller skating rink February 14, 1942 (Box 30)
    - Rural Scenes
      - March 26, 1935, 3 negatives (Box 30)
      - circa April 20, 1936, 6 negatives (Box 30)
      - 1938, 2 negatives (Box 30)
  - Michigan Towns and Counties (non-Washtenaw)
    - Adrian
      - Rural scenes April 21, 1935, 3 negatives (Box 30)
    - Brighton
      - Camp Howell -- Boy Scout camp 1940s, 4 negatives (Box 30)
    - Hamburg
      - R and B Tool Company -- bending machine circa 1949 (Box 30)
    - South Lyon
      - Michigan Seamless Tube Company -- furnace interior February 12, 1947, 2 negatives (Box 30)
    - Wayne County?
      - Sheldon Church dedication June 2, 1946 (Box 30)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Businesses
      - Pioneer Engineering -- equipment at quarry? November 17, 1941, 4 negatives (Box 30)
- Prints
  - Ann Arbor
    - Airports and Airplanes
      - Airplanes and Airports (Box 31)
    - Buildings and Views
      - Churches (Box 31)
      - Gas Stations (Box 31)
      - Hospitals (Box 31)
      - Houses and Businesses
        - Ann Street (Box 31)
        - Ashley (Box 31)
        - Broadway (Box 31)
        - Brooks (Box 31)
        - Division (Box 31)
        - Fair Oaks Parkway (Box 31)
        - Fifth Avenue (Box 31)
        - First Street (Box 31)
        - Forest (Box 31)
        - Fourth Avenue (Box 31)
        - Fuller Road (Box 31)
        - Heatherway (Box 31)
        - Huron (Box 31)
        - Industrial (Box 31)
        - Las Vegas (Box 31)
        - Lawrence (Box 31)
        - Liberty (Box 31)
        - Lorraine Place (Box 31)
        - Main Street, North (Box 31)
        - Main Street, South (Box 31)
        - Maynard (Box 31)
        - Oakland (Box 31)
        - Packard (Box 31)
        - Pontiac (Box 31)
        - Stadium Boulevard (Box 31)
        - State Street (Box 31)
        - State Street -- Nickels Arcade (Box 31)
        - Summit Street (Box 31)
        - University, East (Box 31)
        - University, North (Box 31)
        - University, South (Box 31)
        - Washington (Box 31)
        - Washtenaw (Box 31)
        - William (Box 31)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 31)
      - Parks (Box 31)
      - Railroads
        - Crossings (Box 31)
        - Stations (Box 31)
        - Trains and Wrecks (Box 31)
      - Schools (Box 31)
    - Businesses
      - American Broach (Box 31)
      - Edwards Brothers (Box 31)
      - Ivory Photo (Box 31)
      - King-Seeley (Box 31)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 31)
    - Insurance Claims
      - Fires (Box 31)
      - Storm Damage (Box 31)
      - Traffic Accidents (Box 31)
    - Motor Vehicles
      - Motor Vehicles (Box 31)
    - Organizations and Groups
      - Kiwanis (Box 31)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 31)
    - People
      - People, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Pets and Other Animals
      - Pets and Other Animals (Box 31)
    - Social Life and Customs
      - Community Events (Box 31)
      - Sports (Box 31)
      - Weddings (Box 31)
    - World War II
      - World War II (Box 31)
  - University of Michigan
    - Alumni Activities
      - Reunions
        - Dental School (Box 31)
        - Engineering (Box 31)
        - Law School (Box 31)
        - Literature and Engineering (Box 31)
        - Literature, Science, and the Arts (Box 31)
        - Medical School (Box 31)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 31)
    - Athletics
      - Football
        - Coaches
          - Yost, Fielding (Box 31)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 31)
        - Games and Practices (Box 31)
        - Team Members
          - Harmon, Tom (Box 31)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 31)
      - Swimming (Box 31)
      - Women's Sports (Box 31)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 31)
    - Buildings and Views
      - Aerial Views (Box 31)
      - Alumni Memorial Hall (Box 31)
      - Angell Hall (Box 31)
      - Burton Tower (Box 31)
      - Campus Scenes (Box 31)
      - Dormitories (Box 31)
      - Engineering (Box 31)
      - Gymnasiums (Box 31)
      - Health Service (Box 31)
      - Housing (Box 31)
      - Law Quadrangle and Old Law Building (Box 31)
      - Library (Box 31)
      - Medical Buildings (Box 31)
      - Michigan League (Box 31)
      - Michigan Union (Box 31)
      - Public Health (School of) Building (Box 31)
      - Rackham (Box 31)
      - Stadium (Box 31)
      - University Hospital (Box 31)
      - University Museums (Box 31)
      - Women's Athletic Building (Box 31)
      - Yost Field House (Box 31)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 31)
    - Colleges, Schools, and Other Divisions
      - Broadcasting Service (Box 31)
      - Forestry, School of (Box 31)
      - Law School (Box 31)
      - Library Extension Service (Box 31)
      - Medical School (Box 31)
      - Museum of Anthropology (Box 31)
      - Pharmacy, College of (Box 31)
      - Physics, Department of (Box 31)
      - University Hospital (Box 31)
    - Individuals and Groups, 2 envelopes
      - Individuals and Groups, 2 envelopes (Box 31)
    - Organizations
      - Organizations (Box 31)
    - Special Celebrations and Events
      - Special Celebrations and Events (Box 31)
    - Student Life
      - Bands (Box 31)
      - Dances (Box 31)
      - Fraternities and Sororities (Box 31)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 31)
    - World War II
      - Judge Advocate General's School (Box 31)
      - Reserve Officers Training Corps (Box 31)
  - Dexter
    - Dexter (Box 31)
  - Milan
    - Milan (Box 31)
  - Whitmore Lake
    - Whitmore Lake (Box 31)
  - Ypsilanti
    - Ypsilanti (Box 31)
  - Washtenaw County
    - Washtenaw County (Box 31)
  - Michigan Towns and Counties (non-Washtenaw)
    - Brighton -- Camp Howell (Boy Scouts) (Box 31)
    - Dundee -- Uniloy (Box 31)
    - Lansing (Box 31)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 31)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Buildings and Views (Box 31)
    - Businesses (Box 31)
    - Sports (Box 31)